Guide to the Duke University Libraries Collection of Haggadot, 1200-2003 (bulk1900-2003)
Duke University Libraries Collection of Haggadot 1200-2003 (bulk 1900-2003
- Location List Series, 1200-2003
  - Israel Subseries, 1899-2002, (122 items)
    - The golden Haggadah of Jerusalem / illustration, Jossi Stern; calligraphy, Noah Ophir = Hagadat ha-zahav shel Yerushalayim / tsiyer Yosi Shtern; katav Noah Ofir, 1986., 25 x 34 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadat Volakh: Hagadah shel Pesah le-zekher ha-Sho'ah = The Wolloch Haggadah: Pessach Haggadah in memory of the Holocaust / illustrated by David Wander; calligraphy and micrography by Yonah Weinrib, 1988., 28 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: Hagadat ha-tefutsot / tsiyurim, Shelomoh Kats; targum le-Anglit, G'eremy Haiman = The Diaspora Haggadah: the artistic and transliterated Haggadah of Passover / paintings by Shlomo Katz; English translation by Jeremy Hyman, 1988., 34 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel hidur: Hagadah shel Pesah, 1989., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - 'Arba` hagadot = 4 haggadot: me-'osef Bet ha-sefarim ha-le'umi veha-universita'i bi-Yerushalayim, 1989., 26 x 37 x 3 cm. Illustrated.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah: lefi minhage ha-Sefaradim va-`adot ha-Mizrah] = The Sephardi Haggadah: with translation, commentary and complete guide to the laws of Pesah and the Seder / by Jonathan Cohen, 1989., 25 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah / tsiurim `a.y. Haints Zelig; `itsov Fredrik Gozlan = The Passover Haggadah / illustrated by Heinz Seelig; designed by Frédéric Gozlan, 1990., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - American heritage haggadah: the Passover experience / compiled and edited by David Geffen; English translation by Moshe Kohn; introduction by Stuart E. Eizenstat, 1992., 31 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Palace gates Haggadah = [Hagadah shel Pesah]: parables for the Pesach Seder / compiled by Shalom Wallach; translated by Avraham Sutton; with an interpretative translation of Shir Hashirim, 1995., 25 cm. Text only.
    - Otsar ha-hagadot: bibliyografyah shel hagadot Pesah me-reshit ha-defus ha-`Ivri `ad shenat 720 / ba-`arikhat Yitshak Yudlov, 1997., 35 cm. Text only.
    - Otsar ha-hagadot: bibliyografyah shel hagadot Pesah me-reshit ha-defus ha-`Ivri `ad shenat 720 / ba-`arikhat Yitshak Yudlov, 1997., 35 cm. Text only.
    - The Passover Haggadah / Adin Even-Israel Steinsaltz, 2002., 30 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer Magid mesharim: hu be'ur hadash u-maspik `al Hagadah shel Pesah: `im mavo gadol ... me-eti Netan'el Hayyim b. Mosheh Naman Pape, 1899-1900., 24 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Hagadah for Passover: with English translation, 1901-1902., 16 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: leshon ... `aravi menukad ke-fi minhag ... Bagdad ... ve-gam ke-fi `are Hodu: ve-nosaf `od meturgemet bi-leshon Anglizi, .., 1903-1904., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im be'ur hadash Tavlin le- mitsvah ...: ha-nushah ha-nehugah ule-`umatah nushat ha-Rambam / yatsa le-or `al yede Avraham Aharon ha-Levi Prag, 1909-1910., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah le-lel shimurim: `im be'ur Masa ge ha-hizayon ... / hiber ... Aryeh Leb Frumkin .., 1912-1913., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Sefer Navah tehilah `al Hagadah shel Pesah / ... amarim ... mi-tokh kitve ... Ya`akov David ... me-Radomsk; divre ha-mesader ... Noah Vayntrob, 1926-1927., 21 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 192-?., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah le-Pesah, 1937-1938., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Bet Yisra'el: ve-hu be'ur Hagadah shel Pesah: ... Petah ha-bayit, hemah ha-`inyanim ha-kerovim el peshutah ...: Hadre ha-bayit, hemah ha-`inyanim ha-mitfarshim derekh pilpul ve-derash: ... `Amude ha-bayit hemah `inyanim nifradim gam hu yoreh mekor ha-davar ... / divre ha-mehaber Yitshak Yehoshu`a ...; mi-meni Shim`on Halperin, 1937-1938., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Bet Ya`akov: be'ur `al Hagadah shel Pesah / mah she-hanani d. ... Shim`on Halperin .., 1937-1938., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah le-Pesah, 1938-1939., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: be-'otyot gedolot uve-hirot uve-nikud le-fi nusah Yehude Teman, 1939-1940., 17 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1940-1941., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1941-1942., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1941-1942., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1942-1943., 27 cm. Illustrated.
      Non-Traditional text with traditional elements. Handwritten and typed; mimeographed.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1943-1944., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1943-1944., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1943-1944., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1944-1945., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Non-Traditional text with traditional elements.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1945-1946., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946-1947., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946-1947., 25 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1946-1947., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1946-1947., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 25 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1947-1948., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1947-1948., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1947-1948., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1948-1949., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1948-1949., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Handwritten with a non-traditional text. P. 30 in a different hand than rest of Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1948-1952., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Le-hag ha herut: perakim, 1949-1950., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1950-1951., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1951-1952., 37 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Pessah Hagada., 1951-1952., 41 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Pessah Hagada, 1951-1952., 42 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Facsim. of: Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: bi-leshon ha-kodesh u-fitrono bi-leshon Ashkenazim ... Venitsiyah: Stamperia Vendramina, 501 [1740 or 1741] This Hagada -- printed in Jerusalem by Hamadpis Lipshitz Press, is a reproduction of an old Venetian edition of which the above [as in Facsim. note] is the original title page. It contained an Italian [?] translation, for which English has been substituted--Colophon. Ha-tseva`im veha-tsiurim ve-seder ha-`amudim hut`amu le-tavnit ha-hotsa'at --Colophon. `Al ha-kerikhah tsiur Ha lahma `anya bi-tseva`im mi-tokh Hagadat Sarayevo--Yaari. Yaari 2416
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1952-1953., 18 cm. Illustrated.
      Haggadah written and Illustrated by David Alef.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1953-1954., 34 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im hamishah `asar perushim .., 1953-1954., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1954-1955., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1955-1956., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1958-1959., 27 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1958-1959., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1959-60., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 18 x 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel ha-Seneh le-Pesah, 195-?., 16 x 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 195-?., 20 cm. Illustrated.
      Haggadah handwritten and Illustrated by David Alef. Non-traditional text. Duke owns two copies of this Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 195-?., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder lel Pesah, 196-?., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Haggadah of Passover: Illustrated by David Gilboa, 1961?., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Pardes ha-Hagadah: Hagadah shel Pesah / perushim ... remazim ... dinim ... sipure yetsi'at Mitsraim ba-`arikhat Gedalyah Segal be-siyua` 'Elimelekh He`shin, 1964-1965., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah le-Pesah Me-`avdut le-herut, 1970-71., 30 x 16 cm. Illustrated.
      This modern Israeli Haggadah, put out by the Israeli Defense Force, adds to the traditional story of redemption from Egypt new chapters which tell of the miracles experienced during the creation of the modern state of Israel. The traditional text of the seder appears on the top of each page with new parallels stories from the modern day in smaller print at the bottom of each page. For example, below the traditional four questions are four different questions pointing out the differences between seders of old and modern seders. The first new question points out that in the olden days Jews celebrated Israel leaving Egypt, while in modern days Jews also celebrate Egyptians leaving Israel. The haggadah is illustrated with photographs and illustrations of the Israeli army an other modern Israeli scenes.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 197-?., 27 x 13 cm. Illustrated.
  - Italy Subseries, 1478-1951, (18 items)
    - The Washington Haggadah: a facsimile edition of an illuminated fifteenth-Century Hebrew manuscript at the Library of Congress / signed by Joel ben Simeon; edited by Myron M. Weinstein, 1478., 28 cm. Illuminated.
      Facsimile printed in 1991. Commentary volume included. The Haggadah is signed by 15th Century scribe and artist, Joel ben Simeon. A number of pages contain wine stains as well as notes written in the margins. It is known as the Washington Haggadah because of its location at the Library of Congress in Washington D.C.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, Venetsyah 369 = The Passover Haggadah, Venice 1609 / mavo me-et Betsal'el Narkis, 1609., 35 cm. Illustrated.
      Facsimile printed in Jerusalem in 1974. The Venice Haggada of 1609: introduction (15 p.)inserted. ranslated by Juda-Arie Leon de Modena.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah bi-leshon ha-kodesh uvi-leshon Italyano: `im kamah tsurot `al kol ha-otot veha-moftim asher na`asu la-avotenu be-Mitsrayim, ba-yam uva-midbar ... / ve-gam ba be-tokham pe. Tseli esh ... ve-hu kitsur Zevah Pesah m.h. Rav Don Yitshak Abravan[el] z.l, 1715-1716., 32 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1757-1758., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer hamon hogeg, 1793-1794., 24 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1795-1796., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder agadah shel Pesah, 1805-1806., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Compendium orationum = [Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: kefi minhag Ashkenazim] .., 1828., 20 cm. Text only.
      This Haggadah has a Hebrew text with some Latin on the title page. The majority of the Haggadah only contains the text, however there are four simple illustrations: at the beginning, next to the descriptions of the Matzah and Bitter herbs, and after the final song.
    - Sefer Pi ha-medaber: (notarikon perush Hagadah / mi-meni Yosef bar Rabenu David), 1853-1854., 25 cm. Text only.
    - Seder ha-hagadah shel Pesah, 1864., 32 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: Tri'esti 624 = The Passover Haggadah: Trieste 1864 / mahadurat Avraham Hai Morpurgo; ha-ilustratsyot `a. y. K. Krikhmayer [sic], 1864., 32 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer zikrono le-hayyim: le-zikaron ka'iti ha-nes le-mino be-mile de-Agadata lel hitkadesh hag ha-Pesah ... / ve-hu ha-tsa'ir Hayyim ha-kohen .., 1874-1875., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im tsiurim ve-targum `Aravi: ke-minhag k.k. Bagaad: ... ve-`atah hosafnu vo piyutim nehmadim, tefilat `arvit ... ve-dinim ha-nitsrakhim .., 1886-87., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer Hakam lev / notri. leha-tsa`ir Kamos ben Musa Had'ad, 1886-87., 29 cm. Text only.
    - The Erna Michael wood blocks; twenty nine illustrations from original wood blocks successors of the Venice Haggadah. Introduction by Bezalel Narkiss, 19th Century., 33 cm. Illustrated.
      This is not a Haggadah, as it does not contain any text. This is, however, a collection of 29 imprints made in 1977 from original 19th Century wood blocks based on the famous Venice Haggadah of 1609. The near completeness of the collection of biblical and ritual wood cuts intended for printing is a rare find.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im pitaron be-lashon Italiki `im kamah tsurot ... ve-nosaf ... tefilat `Arvit .., 1903-1904., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah / `im targum u-mavo ve-he`arot be-lashon Italkit me-et Shavtai To'af = Haggadah di Pasqua / testo Ebraico con traduzione Italiana, introduzione e note di Alfredo S. Toaff; illustrata da Eva Romanin Jacur, 1948., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1950-1951., 25 cm. Illustrated.
  - Morocco Subseries, 1943, (1 item)
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Haggadah of Passover: prepared for use of Jewish personnel of the Army and Navy of the United States in French North Africa during the Passover of the year 5703 .., 1943., 24 cm. Illustrated.
  - Netherlands Subseries, 1728-1965, (14 items)
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: im birkhoteha, 1728-1729., 15 cm. Illustrated.
      Handwritten note in Hebrew/Yiddish on the inside of the back cover. Pocket edition of Haggadah limiting its Yiddish commentary to occasional rubrics. It relies on eye-catching initial letters and woodcuts to make the text come alive.
    - Hagadat Moravyah = The Moravian Haggadah, 1737., 31 cm. Illuminated.
    - Seder Hagada le-Fesah, 1764-1765., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Includes a short version of Abarbanel's Zevah Pesah commentary. Wine stains throughout.
    - Helek rishon mi-Sefer arba' yesodot, 1782-1783., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Agadat arba' Kosot, 1817., 18 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah le-lel shikorim, 1849., 19 cm. Text only.
      English title: Haggadah for the Night of Drunks. This is a parody of the Passover Haggadah for use on the holiday of Purim. An example of parodied text: Instead of the son who doesn't know how to ask, this Haggadah has the son who doesn't know how to drink. (p.7). For this son you are instructed to open his mouth for him. Written by Zevi Hirsch Sommerhausen.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah: `im ha`atakah u-hora'at ha-dinim u-ha-minhagim ba-lashon hollandit] = Hagadah, voordragt op de beide eerste avonden van het Paasch-feest: in het Nederduitsch vertaald en met vele ophelderingen voorzien / door G.A. Parser .., 1864., 17 cm. Text only.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah] = Hagadah, voordragt op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met aanwijzing der gebruiken in het Nederduitsch, 1876., 18 cm. Text only.
      Hebrew text with ceremonial directions in Dutch. Missing Pages 35-46.
    - Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah = Hagadah, voordragt op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met Nederduitsche opschriften, 1884., 19 cm. Text only.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah] = Voordracht op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met Nederlandsche opschriften, 1897., 19 cm. Text only.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah] = Hagadah, voordracht op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met Nederlandsche opschriften, 1909., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: een verzameling van gebeden, vertellingen en liederen, ten gebruike voor de Pesach-avondviering: zoowel in huiselijken kring als in gezamenlijke bijeenkomsten, 190-?., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Seder hagadah le-lele Pesah: `im ezeh devarim al mekorah mi-kunteres magid me-reshit le-d.a. landshuteh, ve-`im hora'at ha-dinim veha-minhagim be-lashon hollandit = Voordracht voor de beide eerste avonden van het Paaschfeest: met aanwijzing der voorschriften en gebruiken in de nederlandsche taal / door G.I. Polak, 1926., 19 cm. Text only.
    - The Gospel of Mark: the new Christian Jewish Passover Haggadah, 1965., 25 cm. Text only.
  - Poland Subseries, 1868-1922, (5 items)
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1868., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: `im perush uminhage ... M.h.R.L. mi-Prag, 1905., 24 cm. Text only.
      Commentaries by Judah Loew ben Bezalel (ca. 1525-1609) and Yehudah Yudl Rozenberg (1865-1935).
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im matayim sheloshim u-shemoneh perushim ve-hosafot / me-et maranan ve-rabanan geonim kedoshim .., 1907., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: iberzetst idish mit talmudishe legenden wegen yetsi'at Mitsraim: mit fiel biblishe bilder / bearbaitet durkh H. Niselavits, 1913-1914., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1922., 23 cm. Illustrated.
  - Portugal Subseries, 1928, (1 item)
    - Hagadah shel Pessah': (ritual da ceia Pascal) / traduçao e arranjo de A.C. de Barros Basto (Ben-Rosh), 1928., 19 cm. Text only.
      Haggadah text is in Portuguese only.
  - Russia Subseries, 1993, (1 item)
    - Hagadah shel Leningrad = The Leningrad children's Haggadah = Leningradskaia agada / preface by Adin Steinzaltz; editor in chief I. Dvorkin, 1993., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Haggadah text in Hebrew and Russian; prefatory matter in Russian and English. llustrated by children at a Leningrad Jewish school.
  - Spain Subseries, 1300-1400, (5 items)
    - The Barcelona Haggadah: an illuminated Passover compendium from 14th-Century Catalonia in facsimile (MS British Library Additional 14761) / edited by Jeremy Schonfield; with translations of poems and Targumim by Raphael Loewe; other translations by David Goldstein and Jeremy Schonfield; and contributions by Malachi Beit-Arié .., 14th Century., 27 cm. Illuminated.
    - The Sarajevo Haggadah. Text by Cecil Roth, 14th Century., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Facsimile published in New York in 1966. English introduction by Cecil Roth. The Haggadah consists of 34 full-page miniatures, an illuminated Haggadah text, and hymns and Torah readings for the Passover week. Signed in 1609 by Giovanni Domenico, a church censor. Named because of its location in the Sarajevo Museum. This Haggadah was almost destroyed during the bombardment of Sarajevo in 1994 but was saved by two staff members of the demolished museum where it was housed.
    - The Kaufmann Haggadah, 14th Century., 27 cm. Illuminated.
      Facsimile printed in Budapest, Hungary in 1957. Includes 14 full page miniatures, and a decorated text.
    - The Sarajevo Haggadah. Text by Cecil Roth, 14th Century., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Facsimile of the Sarajevo Haggadah from the 14th Century in Northern Spain. This reproduction was published in New York in 1966. English introduction by Cecil Roth. The Haggadah consists of 34 full-page miniatures, an illuminated Haggadah text, and hymns and Torah readings for the Passover week. Named because of its location in the Sarajevo Museum.
    - The Rylands Haggadah: a medieval Sephardi masterpiece in facsimile: an illuminated Passover compendium from mid-14th-Century Catalonia in the collections of the John Rylands University Library of Manchester, with a commentary and a cycle of poems / [introduction, notes on the illuminations, transcription, and English translation by Raphael Loewe], 15th Century., 34 cm. Illustrated.
      Facsimile was published in New York, 1988. Sephardi text. Commentary by an unidentified author. Introduction in Hebrew and English.
  - Tunisia Subseries, 1945-1950, (2 items)
    - Sefer Ve-higadta le-vanekha: Hagadah shel Pesah be-otyot gedolot `im ... `Aravi: ve-`im kol ha-dinim ha-nitsrakhim be-leshon ha-kodesh uve-leshon `Aravi: ve-nosaf ... Seder u-tikol ke-minhag ... Djerba ... uke-minhag ... Djefotsa ... `im Kidush ha-'arokh minhag Jerba u-piyutim .., 1945-1946., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Sefer Hagadah shel Pesah: ... minhag Djerba ... u-piyut Had gadya ... be-lashon `Aravi, 1950., 22 cm. Text only.
  - United States Subseries, 1869-2002, (193 items)
    - [Hagadah ve-seder shel Pesah] = Form of service for the two first nights of the feast of Passover, 1869., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah ve-seder shel Pesah = Form of service for the first two nights of the feast of Passover / with English translation, 1886., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah ve-seder shel Pesah = Form of service for the first two nights of the feast of Passover: with English translation, 1889., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Front cover serves as an advertisement for The Original Felix Kosher Dining Rooms, a Kosher restaurant and importer of Kosher wines. On the back cover is an advertisement for The Hebrew Standard, a weekly Jewish Journal published in New York during the late 19th and early 20th centuries.
    - Hagadah ve-Seder shel Pesah = form of service for the two first nights of the feast of Passover: with English translation, 190-?., 15 cm. Illustrated.
      Distributed by S.J. Gold, the South's Leading Kosher Delicatessen. Missing from library shelf
    - Seder hagadah shel Pesah = form of services for the first two nights of Passover, with illustrations / revised and edited by Dr. A. Th. Philips, music by H. A. Russoto, 1912., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = Form of services for the first two nights of Passover, with illustrations / revised and edited by A. Th. Philips, 1912., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Includes a special chapter with music for the Passover service composed, selected and arranged by the Rev. Henry A. Russotto.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: mit zekhzig perushim in `ivri taitsh, 1912., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah le-lel shemurim: meduyak hetiv, mesudar yafeh u-meturgam anglit = Service for the first two nights of Passover, 1912., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah mit myuzik noten = Passover Hagadah with music, 1912?., 19 cm. Illustrated.
      This Haggadah has a Yiddish cover page, with an English back cover. The text is in both Hebrew and English. At the end of the Haggadah is the music for four songs. The music is signed by Henry A. Russotto, p. [63].
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im ha`atakah `ivri taitsh ha-meduveret benenu ve-`im perush u-meshalim meha-Rav ha-m.m. mi-Dubna: `im shev`ah tsiurim yafim ve-na`im, 1916., 22 cm. Text only.
      Text in Yiddish and Hebrew Commentary by Jacob ben Wolf Kranz (1740?-1804), who is also known as the Dubnow or Dubner Maggid.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Seder service for Passover eve in the home / arranged by Mrs. Philip Cowen, 1918., 19 cm. Illustrated.
      U.S. Army issued. National Jewish Welfare Board
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Seder service for the first two nights of Passover, with illustrations / revised and edited by Herman Klopper; music composed, selected and arranged by Henry A. Russoto, 191-?., 18 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah be-'otiyot gedolot u-vehirot: mit di dinim vas zainen shaiakh tsu bedikat homets un di sedarim in Idish .., 1921., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Union Haggadah: home service for the Passover / [edited by the Central Conference of American Rabbis], 1923., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Union Haggadah: home service for the Passover / [edited by the Central Conference of American Rabbis], 1923., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1926., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1928., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah `im tsiyurim = Hagadah / arranged by J. D. Eisenstein; illustrated by Lola, 1928., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah le-Bet Ya`akov: `ivrit ve-'idit `im sipurim ve-perushim migdole ha-darshanim u-venam R. Ya`akov mi-Dubna, 1935., 17 cm. Text only.
      Text in Hebrew and Yiddish. Includes commentaries by noted sages, including Jacob ben Wolf Kranz (1740?-1804), who is also known as the Dubnow or Dubner Maggid.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah (The Cowen Haggadah) = The Seder service for Passover eve in the home / arranged by Mrs. Philip Cowen, 1935., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah (The Cowen Haggadah) = The Seder service for Passover eve in the home / arranged by Mrs. Philip Cowen, 1935., 19 cm. Illustrated.